<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Citrus Lab</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="cluster_1">Cluster 1</string>
    <string name="cluster_2">Cluster 2</string>
    <string name="cluster_3">Cluster 3</string>
    <string name="battery_charge">Battery Charge:</string>
    <string name="charging_status">Charging status:</string>
    <string name="battery_temps">Battery Temps:</string>
    <string name="voltage">Voltage:</string>
    <string name="core_control_info">This Controls the state of cpu cores. Helpful for quickly reducing temperature of Soc and saving some battery in exchange for loss of processing power.</string>
    <string name="gov_tunable_info">Allows you to tune CPU governor\'s parameters. This tuning \'may\' help improve performance or reduce battery usage(if done right).</string>
    <string name="cpuset_info">This allows users to select which set of cores are used for different types of tasks mentioned below. This may improve performance or battery life depending on your configuration.</string>
    <string name="display_info">This menu consists of display panel settings. allows users to set refresh-rates and turn on various panel features.</string>
    <string name="cpu_info">This page contains cpu related settings and configuration. Changes made here could have drastic effect on performance and battery.</string>
    <string name="misctemp_info">This page shows various temperature zones and their readings.</string>
    <string name="miscnet_info">This page allows you to change Tcp algorithm which influences your network speed.</string>
    <string name="power_info">This page presents you with power and thermal related settings.</string>
    <string name="prath_about">Helped with android app development. Guiding and teaching me with patience</string>
    <string name="sky_about">Helped with Ui design and pallet selection for app and finding the right people :)</string>
    <string name="sha_about">Implemented Utils tools class and exception handling for shell output handling.</string>
    <string name="memInfo">This page contains settings related to Virtual memory and ZRam. these settings control the memory management and have impact on device performance.</string>

    <string-array name="profile_array" >
        <item>Display</item>
        <item>Cpu</item>
        <item>Gpu</item>
        <item>Power</item>
        <item>Memory</item>
        <item>Misc</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="profileScriptStart">#This is a Citrus Lab Script Auto generated By the App.\n#Do not edit or use this independently unless you know what your doing.\n#The script settings can be edited but at your own risk.\n</string>

    <string name="gpu_info_setfixedfreq">This settings can change your current GPU frequency. Choosing any frequency from this will fix or lock GPU at the chosen frequency.\nIt can be reverted and GPU frequency selection an be handed over to GPU governor by selecting \'Not Selected\' option in choice menu.\nThese frequencies can affect performance of device during gaming sessions.</string>
    <string name="gpu_info_boost_info">This settings sets the GPU boost parameters. This boosting of GPU frequency is done relative to current load on GPU.\nMax/Min Frequency sets the highest/lowest frequency the GPU can boost to.\nBoost frequency sets to what specific frequency the GPU is supposed to boost to on GPU Boost event.</string>
    <string name="power_info_power_sus">This is a driver that manages power. It is responsible for putting device into suspended or low power mode to save battery when inactive.\nThere are few methods it uses to determine weather the device is active or inactive namely \'Hybrid, userSpace, LCD panel, AutoSleep\'.</string>
    <string name="power_info_chg_ctl">This is an app service that controls charging behavior of device.\n\nNormal Charge Threshold:-It stops charging when it hits the temperature mentioned here.\n\nFast Charge Threshold:-It suspends fastCharge and switches to normal charge speeds when it hits the mentioned temperature.</string>
    <string name="power_info_pwr_lmt">This is an Citrus specific driver that limits CPU performance when the device screen is off. It is used to reduce heating and potentially save power especially when tethered to a PC.\nChoosing from low-High sets how aggressive the driver should be in clamping CPU frequencies.</string>
    <string name="mem_info_zram">These settings allows you to control ZRam behaviour.\nZRam is a virtual memory created that speeds up disk transfer and improves app multitasking especially when ram space is running low.\n\nZRam disk size sets the size of the swap file.\n\nZram algorithm sets the desired algorithm for swap logic.\n\nSwappiness sets how often should the memory be swapped(very high values will slow down device).</string>
    <string name="mem_info_vm">These settings allow you to control the virtual memory behaviour.\n\nmin free kbytes:-This is used to force the Linux VM to keep a minimum number of kilobytes free.\n\nExtra free Kbytes:-This parameter tells the VM to keep extra free memory between the threshold where background reclaim (kswapd) kicks in.\n\nDirty ratio:-is the absolute maximum amount of system memory that can be filled with dirty pages before everything must get committed to disk.\n\nVFS cache pressure:-VFS cache pressure motivates code in the kernel to return memory being used for caching to the general pool of free memory.</string>
    <string name="profile_info_default">These profiles are pre made settings that will be applied. they are made for Realme X7 Max/ Mtk D1200. There are three profiles. \n\nPower is used for saving power it reduces performance and responsiveness to save battery.\n\nBalance improves responsiveness while still trying to conserve battery.\n\nPerformance pulls all gpu and cpu to highest settings and is least bothered about saving power and is ideal for gaming.</string>
    <string name="profile_info_custom">These set of toggles helps you to import custom script or add current settings. Users can do the required changes in settings in app and once done during the same session you can generate script from current changes and use that as a profile.\n\nOr users can import custom scripts and apply them on the go.\n\n\'Set On Boot\' option allows users to select a custom profile they want to apply when device boots up.\nSelecting \'Not selected\' clears any profile that is set to execute on boot.</string>
</resources>