<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Citrus Lab</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="cluster_1">Cluster 1</string>
    <string name="cluster_2">Cluster 2</string>
    <string name="cluster_3">Cluster 3</string>
    <string name="battery_charge">Battery Charge:</string>
    <string name="charging_status">Charging status:</string>
    <string name="battery_temps">Battery Temps:</string>
    <string name="voltage">Voltage:</string>
    <string name="core_control_info">This Controls the state of cpu cores. Helpful for quickly reducing temperature of Soc and saving some battery in exchange for loss of processing power.</string>
    <string name="gov_tunable_info">Allows you to tune CPU governor\'s parameters. This tuning \'may\' help improve performance or reduce battery usage(if done right).</string>
    <string name="cpuset_info">This allows users to select which set of cores are used for different types of tasks mentioned below. This may improve performance or battery life depending on your configuration.</string>
    <string name="display_info">This menu consists of display pannel settings. allows users to set refresh-rates and turn on various panel features.</string>
    <string name="cpu_info">This page contains cpu related settings and configuration. Changes made here could have drastic effect on performance and battery.</string>
    <string name="misctemp_info">This page shows various temperature zones and their readings.</string>
    <string name="miscnet_info">This page allows you to change Tcp algorithm which influences your network speed.</string>
    <string name="miscpower_info">This page presents you with power suspend module settings.</string>
    <string name="prath_about">Helped with android app development. Guiding and teaching me with patience</string>
    <string name="sky_about">Helped with Ui design and pallet selection for app and finding the right people :)</string>
    <string name="sha_about">Implimented Utils tools class and exception handling for shell output handling.</string>
</resources>